(Sheldon:)Perhaps what Leonard
is obliquely referring to...
(Sheldon:)...is the occurrence
of sexual dysfunction.
(Howard:)Okay, who had
Leonard gets a floppy disk?
(Sheldon:)Oh. A clever, albeit obsolete, euphemism
for insufficient blood flow...
(Sheldon:)...to the male sex organ.
[CHUCKLES]
(Leonard:)Nothing like that happened, all right?
The sex was just fine.
(Raj:)Just fine?
(Raj:)Oh, dude, the fourth Harry Potter movie
was just fine.
(Leonard:)I'm not saying it was bad.
I'm just saying it wasn't great.
Okay, you mean for both of you?
(Howard:)Because we can totally see it
not being great for her. Am I right?
(Leonard:)To tell you the truth, I think
we were both a little-- I don't know--
(Raj:)-Disappointed? Let down?
-Ashamed? Horrified? Repulsed?
(Leonard:)All I know is
it wasn't the way I dreamed it would be.
[SCOFFS]
(Howard:)Sex is never the way
I dream it's gonna be.
(Raj:)That's because in your dreams,
you're a horse from the waist down.
Excuse me, Wolverine: Origin
Miniseries Issue 2, page 22.
Retractable bone claws.
If you spent less time thinking about sex
and more time on comic books...
...we'd have far fewer
of these embarrassing moments.